Today it's going to get crazy because I have these sparkling glamour bodycon party outfits
and I don't know how they will look. I didn't try them on. There's a lot of sparkling, a lot of
mirror stuff, a lot going on. Thanks to Miu Miu for sending these to me and I'm going to change
into the first one now. I want to point one thing out. I think you can see it better this way. We
have some contouring or fake body contours going on in the fabric here, like printed boots.
So I hope it's going to look awesome. This is crazy!
It's sparkling so much and it fits and it looks like I'm about to go on stage and do some
belly dance acrobatic showpiece I don't know this I've never worn something like this it's crazy
this is the whole outfit now and let me tell you one or two things about it it is one size for one
so it's really stretchy and it does fit really good even though it's one size I mean yes of
course with me the arms could be longer but the legs are really long and it is comfy because the
fabric is really really soft and the fabric is supposed to be skin tone it does not match 100
with my skin tone but it looks close enough and i mean these are not my boobs they're printed on
which also means that the fabric is completely non-see-through, opaque I think.
I'm wearing underwear, you can't really see it. I'm wearing a bra, you can't really see it.
But you can see pretty parts that aren't mine. It's so funny, like fake contouring.
I do have another catsuit which is a bit similar, not as sparkly and it has gloves,
but I'm going to show this one later. For now I have either the mirror dress or different style
is the only thing that does not sparkle today, but I was feeling like doing something elegant too.
So which dress first?
Let's do this one for a change, because they're so sparkly. I need to break from the sparkles.
okay small break from all the glitter before we are starting again but for now it's this
bodycon dress which is super cute i think it's really cute and elegant also front and back side
is simply black but the cut and the fit is really nice like it makes waste my booty looks great in
it my boobs look great in it so I think this is like a really classy dress I also like the cut
here in the breast area cleavage I don't know so it pushes a bit it has these kind of cups and
there are pads inside so it's a bit of a push-up effect and I think this is really like the dress
serious business or if you want to play a super agent female and have a fancy dinner then you
would wear something like this and probably hide this one in your purse to get into that for action
scenes because how cool would that be like a female super hero action hero with this kind of
sparkly catsuit. I don't know. Sorry. Anyway, let's talk about the dress. I paired it with some
fancy heels and I think they look great together.
Yeah, totally adore this look. Maybe I could add a necklace. I didn't have any at hand, which would
like be a really great fit. Maybe you need some diamonds to put on that. Who knows? I don't have
have any diamond necklaces so I'm going bare today which is also nice. I could
put the hair down. So different look. Yeah.
Okay, let's do this as a contrast.
Okay, this is short, really short and so fluffy.
really like poofing poofy and poofing away
again we have the
we have printed on boobs which are huge this time
and we have all these kind of like mirror thingies and oh what i noticed
when i wanted to get into it it has a penny
part
So it's basically a stage outfit. You can do gymnastics with it and have no problem because it is bodysuit with a skirt.
That's basically what it is, yeah. So with the longer mirror parts it's less comfortable than the catsuit here.
Still the fabric itself is very stretchy and very nice to wear.
It's a bit more see-through here. You can tell that I'm wearing a bra underneath.
But I like the design that you have like a built-in collar again.
Anyway, I feel like I have to go dancing somewhere with this one.
Some party, some rave, I don't know.
It's fun. It's a fun one, but I do think I prefer catsuits, so...
Let's do the next catsuit.
last tattoo for this video and yeah sparkly again let me check okay well it's mmm well it's way more
see-through what did I do there approximately 10 hours later okay well
it's way more see-through than the first one I should have worn nude
underwear you can tell that I wear panties and a bra we still have the contour
going on with the kind of fake boobs. Although I think the best look was with
the first one. This also does not look as good as the first one. It looks better
than the dress to be honest. But it's also a nice design. I like the contours and the
lines here. Looks almost like some spacey stay-ups or I don't know we could never
would do this if it wasn't a one piece and it's a bit more toned down than the first one here
I mean it's still a lot and it's still over the top look like some kind of exotic
dancer whatever also with the gloves so there is no stop in the design it's just a nice and
flowy design which I like. If it would not be the nude catsuit parts it would be way too revealing.
I think just having this maybe as a tape or whatever no way I would wear it.
Anyway these are fun outfits. I'm glad I tried them. I think sparkly outfits the first catsuit
still my favorite and then of course this dress because it's not sparkly this
in a third place and then the dress tell me your rating in the comments and leave
a thumbs up and subscribe to my channel check out Miu Miu I'm going to put a
link in the description text and I will see you in the next video have a nice
one bye